我是说 现在没有好看的真人秀了
Look,all I'm saying is,there's no good reality television Anymore.
都是按剧本演的 我想看真实点的
Everything is so scripted. I wanna see something real.
你可以看纪录片嘛
Well,you could just watch an actual documentary.
你当我是拉拉吗
What am I,a lesbian?
企鹅那部挺正常的啊 Morgan Freeman配音的那个
That one with the penguins was pretty legit,with Morgan Freeman?
是指"帝企鹅日记"
伙计 那可是旁白天王
And,man,that guy can narrate.
人家才不管他声音有多温柔激荡
I don't care how SILKY or inspiring his voice is.
我就是不想看企鹅的纪录片
I don't want to see a documentary about penguins.
如果是企鹅们纵酒烂醉
What if the penguins got hammered off of body shots,
几只一组 跑到热水浴缸翻云覆雨呢
formed a couple of alliances,and had night-Vision Sex in a hot tub?
- 接着说 - 这我看定了
- I'm listening. - I'd watch the ass out of that.
我很肯定 企鹅进热水浴缸是自杀
I'm pretty sure penguins wouldn't survive in a hot tub.
我升职了
I got the promotion.-I know!
知道还能怎么拍企鹅吗
You know what else you could do with those penguins,though?
可以找个阁楼圈起来 给它们48小时重新装修
You put 'em all in a loft in tribeca,give 'em 48 hours to redecorate the place...
或者我们可以聊聊你的升职 牛逼耶
or We could talk about your thing.Promotion! Yeah!
我好兴奋 升职以后办公室更大了 而且还配了私人助理
I'm so excited. I get a raise,I get a bigger office,and the best part is,I get an assistant.
- 真不错 - 有助理爽死人的
- Nice. - You're gonna love having an assistant.
懒得做的无聊事 都可以丢给他们
They do all the Boring stuff you don't wanna do,
比如取干洗衣服啦 买周年礼物送...邮递员啦
Like get your dry cleaning or buying anniversary presents for your... your mailman.
我太激动了 因为以前的上司都很恐怖
I am just so psyched,because I have had such terrible bosses,
现在姐要当那种...酷上司
and now I get to be,like,the cool boss,
不是"穿Prada的女魔头" 而是穿工装的俏天使
you know,less "Devil Wears prada," more Angel wears business caszhe.
你应该对下属好点 我高中时的上司就是个混蛋
You should be cool. Okay,in high school,my boss was such a jerk,
所以我故意弄错订单报复他
I used to mess up orders just to get back at him.
Al 你可是在药房打工唉
Al,you worked at a pharmacy.
别让我回想起那些痛苦的日子
Don't make me come in on memorial day.
我了个去
Damn,girl,you sassy!
别把这小姑娘逼急了
Don't make this little white Girl do nothin'.
别把我逼急了
don't make do nothin'.
你们都听见了
y'all heard!
<font color=#38B0DE> -=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- -=http://ytet.org=- Proudly Presents</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译人员: 小王嫂 小王王 奶油灯泡 流沙灯泡 金属灯泡 啦啦灯泡 狗肉灯泡 时间轴: 嘿嘿想数灯泡</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- -=http://ytet.org=- Sync:oùoù??êy??1?</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>幸福终点站 第一季 第13集</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>happy.endings Season 01 Episode 13</font>
跟你说 阁楼配企鹅肯定没收视率
I'm telling you,penguins in a loft is not gonna work.
我貌似看过这种的
I feel like I've seen that before.
如果把企鹅换成虔诚犹太教徒
Now you replace the penguins with hasidic jews
把阁楼换成游艇 那准能红
and you change the loft to a houseboat,you got a show.
犹太游艇 我喜欢
Jews Cruise.I like it.
你知道最好谁来主持吗
You know who would be the awesomest host?
Brooke Burns
Brooke Burns.
美国女星/模特
- Mike Ditka - Mike Ditka
- Mike Ditka. - Mike ditka--
熊队胜率最高的教练 发型永远最棒
all-time winning-est bears head coach,all-time winning-est hair.
花钱雇他肯定来
Pretty sure you could pay him in steak.
好了 姑娘们 两杯啤酒 双份龙舌兰
All right,ladies,two beers,double shot of Tequila.
这不是我点的
I didn't order that.
我知道 但大男人喝桑格里甜酒 我忍不了
I know. I just can't keep serving an ADULT man sangria.
可我喜欢水果味
But I like the fruit.
好吧 我们可以慢慢磨合
Yeah,you and me are gonna have to work on that.
顺便说一下 熊队胜率最高的教练 是George Halas 不是Mike Ditka
And F.Y.I.,the all-time winning-est Bears coach is George halas,not Mike ditka.
那姑娘绝对看上你了 可惜不是你的菜
Dude,that girl's super into you.Too bad she's not your type.
啥 我又没有固定的菜
What? I don't have a type.
拜托 你喜欢小女人型的
Come on,bro.You like girlie girls.
- 彪悍妞不是你的菜 - 我喜欢彪悍妞
- Tough girls aren't your thing. - I like tough girls.
彪悍的...男人
Real tough... men.
你们是说 我把不到彪悍妞咯
So you guys saying I can't handle a tough Chick?
- 没戏 - 哥很彪悍
Nope.I'm tough.
超级彪悍
But I'm super tough.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
- 我是刚才那桌... - 我知道
- I was the guy at the table that you brought the - Yeah.
虽然有点诡异 因为我是顾客 你是服务员
Um,I don't know if this is weird or--'cause I'm a patron,and you work here,but--
赶紧提起您的裙子约我出去吧
oh,just pull up your skirt and ask me out.
其实...这是紧身牛仔裤
Actually,it's,um,a slim-fit... Jean,you know?
没错 我们约会吧
Yeah,let's hang out.
好耶
Yeah! Oh!
听说有个SPA团购 手足护理半价 今晚有空吗
Hey,I just heard about this midweek spa deal-- 2-for-1 mani-pedis.You wanna go tonight?
我不行 今晚得去做瑜伽
Ah,I can't. I have pilates.
啊哦 你是问Jane呢
Oh,you meant Jane.
我也去不了
I can't go either.
要参加成人扫盲机构的活动
I've got a meeting for my adult literacy organization.
我得开始做点有意义的事了
I need to start doing more good,you know?
我能来帮忙么
Hey,maybe I could help.
我觉得你不会喜欢的
Yeah,I don't think you'd like it.
工作繁重 要做计划 还要耐心陪他们耗
It is a ton of work,with the planning and the patiently sitting around,
等他们去认那些无敌简单的词
waiting for them to sound out even the simplest words.
去不成是你赚到了 相信我
Eee.It's--you're not missing anything.Trust me.
好吧 那咱就回见了
Okay,well,I guess I'll see you guys later then.
- 早餐什么的 多谢了 - 不客气
- Thanks for breakfast. - You're welcome.
我知道 这么做不够仗义
I know,I know.That was a crappy thing to do.
但是吧 这个扫盲小组是属于我的
It's just that this literacy group is my thing,
然后Alex总抢走全部注意力
and Alex always has a way of kinda coming in and stealing all the attention.
公元89年 图密善大帝下令修建地下墓穴
In the year A.D.89,Titus flavius domitian ordered the construction of the hypogeum catacombs--
20年前
*****
爸爸你看 我是马蹄鞋大帝
look at me,daddy! I'm emperor cloppy-Shoes.
瞧瞧咱妞!
look at you!
哒哒 哒哒
Cloppy,cloppy.
哒哒 哒哒 哒哒哒
Cloppy,cloppy,cloppy.
耐死人了 大宝贝
Oh,you're adorable,honey.
我努力筹备很久了
I've been working on this thing for so long.
这次毕业典礼算是我闪耀的机会
I mean,the graduation is kinda my time to shine.
当然他们是主角 但我也是一分子
I mean,also the readers' time to shine,but me,too,
我一直在准备主持人讲稿的段子
'cause I've been working on my emcee jokes,and...
反正吧 这事对我超重要的
this Whole thing is just super important to me.
不好意思
Sorry.
我忍不住去脑补你妹妹的小脚 套着你爹的鞋
I can't stop thinking about your sister's little feet in your Dad's shoes.
肯定超好笑的
Must have been hilarious!
- 嗨 瑞瑞 - 嗨 潘潘
- Hey,ree-ree! - Hey,pee-pee!
这些爱称什么的 我们正经需要头脑风暴一下
Yeah,we're gonna need a little brainstorming session on my Nickname.
这是你干洗的衣服 还有你的新手机
Here's your dry cleaning and your new cell phone.
私人号码都传到新手机上了 旧手机就纯工作用了
I transferred your personal contacts to your new one so you can use the old one for work.
看起来蛮复杂的
Hey,this looks complicated.
刚对着自己的乳沟咔嚓了下
and I just took a picture of my cleavage.
然后又电邮给我继父了
and,yep,I just e-mailed it to my stepdad.
瑞瑞 稍微等下
Oh,hey,ree-ree,one tiny scooch.
账单上说 你从店里划卡兑了50块现金
It says here on the bill you got $50 cash back?
天呐 你不说我就全忘了
Oh,my god.I totally forgot to mention that.
我花了10块买午餐 然后急着取手机 没时间去银行
I just used $10 for lunch.I was getting your phone.I didn't have time to go to the bank.
太不好意思了 等我把剩下的还你
I am so sorry.Let me get you your change.
瑞瑞 别这样 我是酷老板的
Ree-ree,come on.I'm the cool boss.
像Tina Fey那样的
I am like Tina Fey,okay?
紧急时借点现金 我完全不介意的
And I am totes down with you borrowing a little extra cash-ish in an emergency.
好吧 那多谢了
Okay.Thanks.
幸好你把找头收着了 否则我也会砸在房租或者杂货店的
You just pocket that change 'cause I probably would've blown it on rent or Groceries.
有批萨 有体育新闻 容我多嘴一句
Pizza,we've got "Sportscenter," and not to go out on a limb here,
哥滚床单还是很有水平的 是吧
but that was some pretty dece lovemaking,if I do say so myself.Am I right?
必须的 水平蛮高
Yeah,totally. It was really,really fine.
满屋长曲棍球的东西是怎么个说法
So,uh... What's--what's up with All the lacrosse stuff?
我是丙级女子曲棍球队的教练
I'm a division 3 Women's lacrosse Coach.
那咋还去当服务生
Then why do you waitress?
因为我是丙级女子曲棍球队的教练
Because I'm a division 3 Women's lacrosse coach.
对哦
Right.
不错呢
Cool.
你刚才说水平蛮高 是说一般般高
So when you said before that the lovemaking was fine,did you mean just fine,
还是"须做一生拼 尽君今日欢"那种高
or did you mean,like--like,'90s fine,like,"girl,you're so fine"?
怎么说呢 还不错啦
you know,it was good.
我只希望下次能更...刺激点
I just was hoping next time we could be... a little more adventurous?
我是说 你都没有过什么幻想吗
I mean,haven't you ever had any fantasies?
我一直幻想在瀑布下来一发
well,I have always fantasized about doing it under a waterfall
又或在森林里 再或是房间里 周围摆上几千只蜡烛
or maybe in the woods or maybe in a room,surrounded by thousands of candles,
白色纱帘被风吹得让人想入非非
white,shrouded curtains blowing in from the wind outside.
所以你的性幻想都是 Color Me Badd的音乐录影带场景吗
So you want to have sex like you're in a color me badd video?
差不多
Kinda.
又或者咱放他们的歌当背景乐 然后自己拍录影带
Well,maybe we can play color me badd in the background while we make our own video.
向Color Me Badd致敬的那种吗
Like a color me badd tribute video?
- 唔...你是说性爱录影带 - 嗯呢
- Oh,you mean a sex tape. - Yeah.
- 这想法真不错 - 就是说啊
- That makes so much more Sense. - Yeah.
Penny不会用新手机 总是误拨电话给我
Penny keeps pocket-dialing me from her new Phone.
<font color=#38B0DE>How will I know if he really loves me
how will I know if he really loves me?
<font color=#38B0DE>- I say a prayer with every heartbeat</font> - 够了啊喂
- I say a prayer with Every heartbeat - Come on!
别动气啊
Don't hate!
<font color=#38B0DE>I fall in love whenever we meet
I fall in love whenever we meet
<font color=#38B0DE>- I'm asking you</font> - 太可怕了
- I'm asking you - oh,that's terrifying.
是啊 人间能得几回闻啊
Yet,it's all I want to listen to ever again.
所以...我们要让毕业日变成必耶日
So... Graduation Sunday is gearing up to be quite the funday.
真是等不及看学员们露几手了
Can't wait for our new readers to show off their skills.
先说吃的 Lauren 你准备三份乳蛋饼
Food--Lauren,I have you down for three quiches,
Barbara准备两份 Keisha准备两份火腿
Barbara,two quiches,and,Keisha,two hams.
Keisha和乳蛋饼发音相似
我知道 笑点足足的
I know,I know. It's hilarious.
但是段子先摆一边 真心需要那些火腿哦
But,uh,all jokes aside,we're counting on those hams.
女士们 让我们一齐敬Jane 感谢她的尽心计划和辛勤工作
Ladies,let's all thank Jane for her tireless planning and hard work.
敬Jane
- To Jane. - Jane.
哎呦 尽力而为啦
Oh,well,I do my Best.
女士们
Hi,ladies.
这位是谁
Oh,who's this?
我妹妹 Alex
That's Alex,my sister.
你怎么来了 Al
Whatcha doing here,al?
我指甲做到一半 突然顿悟
Well,I was in the middle of my mani-pedi,and I realized,
我糟蹋这时间干啥
you know,what am I doing with my time?
于是我上了网 查到2/3的文盲都是女性
So I went online,and did you guys know that two-thirds of illiterates are women
98%的文盲来自发展中国家
and that 98% of illiterates come from developing countries,
"教皇"一词其实源于希腊文 原意是"父亲"
and the word "Pope" Is actually from the greek "Pappas," which means "Father"?
抱歉 身陷维基百科 迷上就难以自拔了
I'm sorry.I got caught up in a wikipedia hole,and once it has you,you can't get out.
就...
So... whew! -Ha ha!
你们这是干啥捏
So what are we doing,y'all?
"捏"
"Y'all"?
我们在为学员筹办毕业活动呢
we were just planning our graduation event...For our new readers.
太有趣了 其实我有个小想法
Oh,how fun. I actually had a thought on that,too.
不如我们做字母形状的饼干吧
What if we served sugar cookies in the shape of letters?
你们觉得怎么样
What do you think?
我不...
no,I don't...
这主意太有才了吧 Jane
it's a genius idea,right,Jane?
- 没错 有才 - 就灵光一闪
- Yes. Yes.Genius. - it came to me.
谢谢
Thank you.
又发生了 Brad
It's happening again,Brad.
Alex席卷而来 所有人都倾心于她
Alex swoops in,and everyone falls all over themselves
就凭她一句"我们能做字母饼干吧"
because she says,"Oh,hey,I'll make cookies in the shapes of letters."
太有才了
That's genius.
有才 有吗
Genius? Really?
得了 亲爱的 你太小题大做了
Come on,babe.You're making too big a deal of this.
大家都知道你的辛勤工作 比她的饼干更有意义
Everybody knows your hard work means more than her cookies.
不过给我留个"B" 它们最棒了
Save me a "B," though. They're the best.
它们都一个味儿
They all taste the same.
不过"B"代表我名字嘛
But the "B" is for my name.
哥们 不是要吃中饭吗 咋还不梳洗打扮
dude,I thought we were going to lunch. Why aren't you dressed?
Penny整夜都没关机
Penny didn't turn her phone off all night.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我一直在听她的疯狂人生
I mean I've been listening to her insane life.
过去的24小时里 我听到她靠调情逃避违章罚单
Over the past 24 hours,I've heard her flirt her way out of a parking ticket,
然后勾搭过敏症专科医师
flirt her way into a date with an allergist,
面对大桶八喜 各种傲娇加纠结
and have an extremely long and awkward standoff with a quart of Cherry Garcia.
这是最棒的真人秀 "Penny企划"
It's the best New reality show. "Project: Penny."
哥们 这么做是不道德的
Dude,that is so wrong.
我知道 但这个狂上瘾的
I know.It's also insanely addictive.
配角们更是难以置信
And the supporting cast is unbelievable.
拉丁辣妞助手Rita 是忠臣还是反贼
I mean,the new,fiery latin assistant Rita-- LOYAL EMPLOYEE or crazy grifter?
由您判定 现在她俩正在一起
You be the judge. She's with her now.
你想明天请假去过斋月吗
You want to take off tomorrow for ramadan?
墨西哥人难道不能信伊斯兰教咩
Now there can't be muslim mexicans?
不 当然可以
Oh,no,there can.
不过你昨天早退了 理由是参加外甥的基督教洗礼
It's just that you also left early yesterday for the christening of your nephew j??????sus morales.
- 好 我要加入 - 很好
- Okay,I'm in. - Yeah.
击个掌 不给算了
high five. No?
给你来条毛巾吗 头箍神射手
All right. Can I get you a towel,Patrick Ewing from the free-throw line?
- 就是 娇艳滴滴的花仙子 - 你说啥
- Yeah,drippy longstocking. - Excuse me?
我下次会改进的
I can do better.
伙计们 我得立马塑形
guys,I gotta get in shape quick.
那女服务生想拍性爱录影带
The waitress from Rosalita's wants to make a sex tape.
- 那真是绝逼... - 我说吧
- Wow,that is an awesome... - I know!
...的烂
Ly... bad Idea.
伙计 你不上镜啊
Yeah,you're not good on camera,bro.
还记得新闻班第三年那回吗
Remember Journalism Class junior year?
体育方面 小熊队得到...触地得分
And in sports,the cubs played the,uh,san--Touchdown.
我能吃个三明治吗
Can I get a-- can I get a sandwich?
自那时起 哥上镜头那是家常便饭
I've been on camera plenty of times since Then.
05年公牛队比赛的亲吻镜头 神作
Uh,bulls game,'05,kiss cam-- nailed it.
好吧 如果你要拍 有几点注意事项
Okay,if you're gonna do this sex tape,couple things--
第一 确保她从你右脸角度拍 因为你左脸巨恐怖
one--make sure she shoots you from the right side,'cause from the left,you look like a troll.
第二 去晒一下 你太白了
Two--get a Tan.You're pretty white.
就像白斩鸡似的
You're like the ghost of Tilda Swinton.
第三 左脸的问题我是认真的
Three--I was super Serious about that troll thing,
不是长发飘飘的白骨精那种恐怖
and not a like a "Cute doll with the hair" Troll,
而是追杀哈利的伏地魔那种恐怖
like a "distract you with a crystal and steal your baby" Troll.
- 没错 - 看这边 有木有
- Yeah. - Look at him--like there.
没错 就是这边
- Yeah,there is is. - Where?
这边正常 转过来吓死你
There it's fine,and then ooh.Cheese.
Tizley...Tiz...
"Tizley. Tizley. Tiz..."
Tizzle-Top-tufted Mazurka
"Tizzle-Top-tufted mazurka."
好吧 我的错
- "Mazurka." - You know,my bad.
我不应该选这本书 85%都是虚构的词
I shouldn't have picked a book with 85% made-up words.
- 是啊 - 对不起
- Yeah. - Sorry.
你好 我叫Alex 是Jane的妹妹
Hi.I'm Alex,Jane's sister.
我是Paul 很高兴见到你
Hi.I'm Paul.Very nice to meet you.
好了 我要走了 毕业典礼见咯
Okay,so I gotta run. So I will see you at graduation?
好啊 88
Yes."C-U" Then.
不过哦 拜拜不该这么读的
That is not actually how you spell "See" Or "You."
- 好了 - 再见 Paul
- Okay. - Bye,Paul.
我能用下你的搅拌器吗
Can I borrow your mixer?
饼干的事 先别操之过急 Al
Well,you know,you might want to hold off on the cookies,al.
你走了以后 她们议论纷纷 对这主意貌似并不感冒
After you left,the women were talking,and they--they weren't really into the idea.
什么 我以为她们喜欢呢
What? I thought they loved it.
是啊 估计她们是怕引起学员的困惑
Yeah,but I guess they thought they could be a little confusing to the students,too.
面对一根竖棍的饼干 是小写L 还是大写I呢
I mean,is the cookie a lowercase "L"? is it a capital "I"?
这会让毕业学员们大为受挫的
I mean,something like that,for a new reader,could really set 'em back.
大写I两端的横线可以突出一些
We can put the little thingies on the I's to clarify.
其实问题不在于是否突出衬线 Al
You know,I don't think this is a serif issue,al.
我想解释的说 但他们很坚持己见
I mean,I tried to talk to them,but they were-- I mean,they were really firm on this one.
啊哦 也许我本不该来
Wow. Maybe I just won't come at all then.
真衰 不过我能理解
Ooh. That's a bummer,but I totally get it.
做你自己该做的吧
You gotta do you.
真不敢相信 我们也艳照门了一把
I can't believe that we made a sex tape.
可不嘛 想不想观赏下
I know.You wanna watch it?
已经成片了吗 那走起来吧
Already? Yeah,pop it in.
走着
Okay.
哇 那是我啊
Oh,look,it's me.
你这么自信的走过来 我超喜欢的
I love how you're coming at me here,all confident.
- 很耐人 - 谢谢夸奖
- Super Cute. - Thank you.
但是这里你就让我彻底崩溃了
But This is where it all starts to fall apart for me.
第一个吻稍微有点敷衍哦
Your first kiss is a little sloppy.
满脸都写着心不在焉 大概是因为你失去了平衡
You're all over the face,probably 'cause your balance is off.
叉腰肌很没劲 看到没
It's a core-strength Issue. See?
我们还是快进到最后两分钟 好不
Let's jump ahead to the last two minutes,shall we?
你有满腔的激情 但是基本的技术却没有掌握好
You have got a ton of raw ability,but your fundamentals are off.
这影响到了你的力度 你的节奏
It affects your footwork,your rhythm.
这又怎么了
What's happening?
当你上了三垒后
By the time you get into the red zone,
你气喘吁吁了 完全忽视了对手的动作
you're exhausted and you're barely paying attention to what the other team is doing at all.
嘭 你错失了得分的良机
Boom.You missed a major scoring Opportunity.
瑞瑞 甲方公司送了几瓶伏特加 你要吗
Hey,ree-ree,that liquor company We did that event for sent over a few bottles of vodka.You want one?
早就下手了 潘潘 我已经揣走两瓶了
Way ahead of you,pee-pee. I already grabbed a couple.
想来点吗
Want to try some?
- 算了吧 - 这可是好东西
- I'm all set. - It's good stuff.
现在才中午啊
It's noon.
这个可不对 兄弟
This is bad,man.
酷老板这招绝对她不管用
The cool boss Thing's not working for her at all.
瑞瑞在揩油 我们得告诉Penny去
Ree-Ree's totally taking advantage.We gotta talk to Penny.
我们不能去 要不偷窥就露馅了
We can't. Then she'll know we've been spying on her.
且若我们干涉 就与其他真人秀同流合污了
Plus,if we step in,we're no better than all the other bad reality Shows.
我们必须遵守纪录片的规矩
We gotta respect the Documentarian's code.
真的吗 所以你不能破坏这个规矩
Really? So this code you can't break,
却可以盗用别人的信用卡租船是吗
but the "Don't apply for a boat license in my name" Code is fair game?
我怎么可能用你的信用卡租船呢
Well,how am I supposed to rent a boat using your credit card?
Alex 很高兴见到你
Alex,hi. Good to see you.
真的吗 Barbara
Oh,is it good to see me,Barbara?
那是你的真名吗
If that's even your real name.
- 什么 - 我真不理解你们这些人
- Excuse me? - I can't believe you guys.
我满怀兴奋地来帮忙 你们起初假装喜欢我的主意
I come over here,excited to help people,and then you pretend to like my ideas,
我一走 你们却说那些主意蠢
and as soon as I leave,you call them Dumb.
Alex 没人这么说啊
Alex,no one said that.
当Jane说毕业典礼时 你要去未来世界主题公园 我们都很失望
We were all sad when Jane told us you'd be out of town for the graduation,at epcot.
该给饼干喷糖霜了
Time to Frost the letter cookies!
好啦 我这有A E I...哦
Okay,I have "a," "E," "I"... oh.
AEIOU是英语的五个元音字母
你
You.
你为啥骗我 还说我去未来世界公园了
Why would you lie to me? And why would you say I went to epcot?
- 具体得有点变态了吧 - 人家害怕嘛
- That is so weirdly specific. - I panicked.
好吧 我知道这样做并不光荣
Okay,look,al,I am not proud of my behavior.
我知道这样很猥琐
I know that it's Petty.
只是我付出很久了 我太在意了
It's just--I work really hard for a long time on something,it's my thing,
而你却在最后一秒冲进来 博取了所有人的注意
and then you just swoop in at the last second and steal all the attention,
所有人都"哇唔"的赞不绝口
and everyone goes,"Ooh!"
我完全不知道你在讲什么 我要走了
I have no idea what you're talking about,but I'm outta here.
"哇唔"
"Ooh!"
她用教练的眼光看你们的性爱录像吗
So she broke your sex tape down like it was game film?
是啊 而且她也没夸我技术好
Yeah,and she wasn't super complimentary Either.
老兄 她可是教练 那都是建设性意见
Dude,she's a coach.It's constructive Criticism.
而且去年罗克福德大学女子球队 成绩是3胜27负
Fact--last year,rockford university's women's lacrosse team-- 3 and 27.
今年可是29胜1负
This year--29 and 1.
就因为教练换成了Kim Groff
Only difference-- New Coach Kim Groff.
她是个赢家 老兄
She's a Winner,dude.
怎么啦 我不能人肉你炮友吗
What? I can't google your lady?
她这么棒 反而让人别扭
It sorta sucks because she's kinda awesome.
- 她也有怪嗜好嘛 - 怪嗜好?
- So she has one little foible. - foible?
谁知道呢 也许是福不是祸
Who knows? Maybe in the end,it'll be a positive.
我们都能因此学会更多 取悦三角区的技巧
We can all stand to learn a little bit more about the old bathing suit area.
当然"我们"指的是"你们" 因为我是个天才
Of course by "We all," I mean "You guys," 'cause I'm gifted.
快些重振旗鼓 老兄
You gotta get back on the horse,dude.
强者不会因为一时不顺就不思进取
The greats don't quit after one bad day.
我是说 艳照门以后陈老师放弃了吗
I mean,did babe Ruth Quit after His Sex Tape was criticized?
没有 他已经要回娱乐圈了
No,he went right out and made Another sex Tape.
我知道 宾客名单本该在两小时前发过去
I know. That guest list was supposed to be sent over two hours ago.
实在抱歉 麻烦您稍等一会儿
I am so--I am so sorry.Could you please hold?
Rita 你今天跑哪去了 我都要忙死了
Rita,where have you been all day? I'm slammed.
我家里有急事
Uh,I had a family emergency.
在购物中心吗
At the mall?
我一会给您回电 我们得谈谈
I'm gonna call you right back.We gotta talk.
Rita 是不是因为姐是酷老板 就占我便宜
Rita,I feel like you're taking advantage of me 'cause I'm the cool boss.
我懂了 就因为我是墨西哥人
Oh,I get it.This is because I'm mexican.
不是的 在单位我们应各司其职
No. This is just,you know,in a work environment,we both have roles--
承认吧 潘潘 你是个种族主义者
face it,pee-pee. You're a racist.
什么
What?
Rita这么快就打出种族牌了
Wow.Rita's going to the White-guilt angle pretty Fast.
是啊 哥努力了好几年才成功
Yeah,took me years to do that with you guys.
顺便提一句 电视能给我吗
By the way,can I have your tv?
你懂的 奴隶制什么的
You know,slavery and whatnot?
我绝对不是种族主义者
I am so not a racist.
我的初恋是危地马拉人
I mean,the first guy who felt me up was a guatemalan.
是不是还要举例说自己有黑人朋友呢
next you'll be telling me you're not a racist because you have a black friend.
但我有 确实有
But I do.I do.
我们得做点什么
We gotta do somethin'.
我爱"Penny企划" 但这太离谱了
I mean,I love "PROJECT: Penny," but this has gone too far.
是啊 瑞瑞要惹哭潘潘了 让她去屎吧
Yeah,ree-ree's making pee-Pee Cray-Cray.It's time for her to go downtown.
别 好好说话
No.You say the words regular.
没想到你会回来啊
I didn't think I'd be seeing you again.
为啥 以为我怕了吗 我没怕
Why,because I was intimidated? Because I wasn't.
一起来活动筋骨吧
Let's get physical.
再看一遍怎么样
Pop that tape in again,would you?
好啊
Ooh. Okay.
咋小腿这么瘦弱 貌似不是我吧
Wow. I did not realize my calves were so defined,and that is not me.
没看错
Oops. Wrong Dave.
但我分析时 感觉你能学到不少东西呐
But while I have it up,you could actually learn something from this guy.
他用了一个非主流站位 但是那也是他的力量源泉
See,he's got an UNORTHODOX wide stance,but that's where all his power comes from.
对了 你知道该看什么吗
Oh! You know who you should check out?
Jason 2008年秋 落叶堆野战 视野不太好 但是...
Jason,fall 2008.We were in a piles of leaves,so it's kinda hard to see,but--
那个...我闪人了
and... I'm out.
您是Rita吗
Rita?
头发过深了 Rita吗
Too Brown.Rita?
- Rita吗 - 是你哦
- Rita? - Rita.
Rita Rita Rita
Rita,Rita,Rita.
我们知道你一直在 占你老板Penny Hartz的便宜
We know you've been taking advantage of your employer,penny Hartz.
你们是谁
Who are you?
公司安保 我是高级专员Maxfield.
Company security. I'm senior agent Maxfield.
他是我的手下 Bradson
This is my junior agent,Bradson.
其实我们很平等
Ah,we're actually pretty equal.
都是政治关系 他爸是公司老板 所以...
It's Political.His dad owns the company,so...
都是我自己打拼来的 活在老爹阴影下很困难的
I think I've earned it on my own merits,plus it's been Harder for me 'cause of my father.
自说自话
Debatable.
问题在于 我们有你行为不当的罪证
The point is,we have evidence of criminal misconduct.
公司里到处都是监控摄像
We got cameras Everywhere.
你桌上的订书器 不是摄像
that stapler on your desk-- not a camera.
- 嗷嗷 - 接着猜啊
- Boom. - Keeping you guessing.
摄像在哪儿 无所不在
Where are the cameras? Everywhere.
伙计们 求求你么 你们让我干什么我都答应
Guys,please,okay,I'll do anything you want.
我会把从公司偷的钱全都还回去
I'll give back all the money that I stole from the company.
- 嗯... - 当...当然
- Uh... uh,M-mon -Yeah.Y-Yeah.
- 把钱都还了 - 一定要还了
- Give back the money. - Definitely do that.
但在这之前 你还得先做一件事
But before you definitely do that,we need you to do something else,too.
我错了
I was wrong.
您不是种族歧视分子
You're not a racist.
您有曼德拉的胸怀 奥巴马夫人的身材
You have Nelson Mandela's heart and Michelle Obama's arms.
但我还是辞职好了
But I'm afraid I'll have to quit.
什么 为什么
What? Why?
我不配给你打杂
I don't deserve you.
他也不配...那个过敏专科医生
Neither does that... allergist that you're dating.
- 没错 - 从没见过你这么好的上司
- You're right. - You're the coolest boss I've ever Had.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 再见 潘潘 - 再见 瑞瑞
- Good-Bye,pee-pee. - Bye,ree-ree.
想问你点事
okay. I gotta ask you something.
没错 有时候你是喜欢出风头
Yes,sometimes you like to make yourself the center of attention.
什么 你怎么知道
What? How did you know that?
Alex 都认识你这么久了
Alex,I've known you for a long time.
知道你的想法
I know how you think.
- 真的吗 - 好吧 是Jane跟我说的
- Really? - No,of course not.I talked to Jane.
要真把你看透了 就不会迷惑 你为啥买这条猴子烧烤的围裙了
If I knew how you thought,I'd understand why you bought me this apron
with a picture of a monkey standing next to a barbecue pit.
上面写着"猩猩之火 可以烧烤"
It says "King of the grill-a."
我看得懂哈
Yeah,I read the apron.
我真那样么 爱抢风头吗
Do I really do that? Do I steal attention?
这么说吧 婚礼之后 反正大家谈论的不是花
Let's just say after our wedding,no one was talking about the flowers.
好吧 Jane肯定知道 你不是故意抢风头
Okay,look,I'm sure deep down,Jane knows that you don't intentionally try to steal focus.
但这也很伤人的
It doesn't mean that it hurts her any less.
没错
Yeah.
关键在于"猩猩"之火 不是"星星"
The word "Grill" As in "Gorilla." That's the Point.
毕业典礼
"Mittens先生意识到 追他的那只黑猫..."
"Mr. Mittens realized the black cat chasing him..."
开玩笑吧 又是Q 到底有多少问题(Quentins)
seriously? Another "Q"? how many quentins were they expecting?
"...以及他新交的好友"
"...and his new Best friend."
- 棒极了 Ellen - 谢谢
- That was great,Ellen. - Thank you.
- 那书是图书馆借的吗 - 不是
- Is that a library book? - No.
说到图书馆借书 怎么处理滞期罚金呢
Speaking of library books,what is the deal with library fines,huh?
啊交吧 就是阿娇 懂了没
I'd rather have Ralph fiennes.Right,ladies?
灭哈哈
Ha ha!
有请Paul Petley 朗读郑渊洁的"舒克和贝塔"
All right,next up,we have Paul petley reading "If I ran the zoo" By Dr.Seuss.
如果这套童话大王是琼瑶阿姨写的呢
What if it were written by Dr.Dre instead?
那就不是童话大王了 就是童话大娘了
It wouldn't be "Hooked on phonics."It'd be "Hooked on chronic"... what?
挺搞笑的嘛
Come on.
Paul Petley 大家欢迎
All right.Paul petley,Everyone.Okay.
实际上 我不会读这本书了
Actually,I'm not gonna be reading "If I ran the zoo" Right now.
而是一篇特别的信
Instead,I'm gonna be reading a very special letter.
亲爱的Jane 你是一位女强人
"Dear Jane,you are an amazing person."
是我的奋斗目标
"I want to be you. "
你不在时 我曾去试穿你的衣服
I used to go into your closet when you weren't around and put on your clothes.
我懂了
" All righty. "
你是我姐 我从没想过抢你的风头
You're my sister,and I never meant to steal your spotlight.
你设立了标杆
"You set such a high standard.
我一直都在追赶
"I've spent my whole life trying to keep up. "
你是非常...出...
You are an e-exta-- "Exta-Ex-extraor... or..."
非常出色的人 也是最好的姐姐 我爱你
"Extraordinary person and the best sister ever. I love you."
真对不起 我就一傻子
I'm--I am so sorry.I feel like an idiot.
不知道该怎么说
It's just,I don't know.
有时候嘛 我想成为逗乐众人的焦点
Sometimes I wanna be the one that comes in and makes everyone laugh.
但不该排挤你
But I never should have excluded you.
我不介意
It's okay.
说实话 我对这些还真没兴趣
Honestly...  I'm not interested in any of this anyway.
这事可以回头聊
So... okay,we can talk about that later.
谢谢
Thanks.
Oh,yeah.-Thank you.
小正太 你叫什么名字
Whoa.Hey.What's your name?
Kevin
Kevin.
那你为啥选B字母饼干呢 Kevin
Then why you,uh,taking the last "B" Cookie,Kevin?
我叫Brad 这是我的
I'm Brad.That's my cookie.
给我
Gimme that.
你也应该尝尝
You should try one of these.
不过没你的
Not today,though.
咋啦
what?
好吧 分点给你
We'll split it.